欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
这些肉丸子都是现做的哈
These fresh meatballs in here?
我得夹俩玉米棒
Gotta get that corn on the cob
带不带棒子 都是老玉米
On the cob, off the cob, it don't matter.
你们这还真不是闹着玩的
Y'all ain't playing around this motherfucker
这他妈是什么东东啊
What the fuck is this right here?
你们现在不提供吃龙虾的围兜了吗
You guys don't have the lobster bibs no more?
-抱歉噢  -我的天啊
Sorry, hon. - Oh, my God.
又来一盘 你疯了吧
Another plate? Are you out of your mind?
它宣传标语上不写着尽情享用吗 那就吃啊
It says all you can eat, right? So you fucking eat.
是啊我知道 但你这
Yeah, I know, but still.
你真是火力全开啊 伙计
You are really going at it, man.
让我问问你这个 你有想过
Let me ask you this question. Have you ever considered
你一生会浪费多少时间在尿尿这件事上吗
how much time you've wasted in your life urinating?
-几百个小时  -太他妈对了
- Hundreds of hours You're fucking right.
我是说 那个时间可以用来
I mean, you could be learning something
学好多东西啊
in that time, you know?
谁能摇身一变成为亿万富翁
You know who's gonna be a billionaire?
能造出 把尿液当能源这种汽车的人
Motherfucker who's gonna, uh, create a car that runs on piss.
-是啊 你猜怎么着  -这样就不会再浪费时间了
Yeah. You know what? - No more time wasted.
你这愣脑瓜终于
Now that idiotic brain of yours has finally...
想象一下开着这车横穿全国
You're driving across country- -
想出好点子了
You've landed on something. Yeah.
喝点什么水啊 佳得乐啊
You drink water and Gatorades and shit,
-或者咖啡啊 反正逮着什么喝什么  -嗯
- fucking coffees and shit the whole fucking trip. - Yeah.
然后你靠边停车 释放一下你的老二
You pull over, take your dick out,
把它塞进那个小排气管里
put it in that little hole where the gas goes,
尿满那玩意儿
and fill that motherfucker up.
然后继续开心地开吧 尿车
You're on your merry way. The Peeus.
就他妈的叫这个了 尿车
That's what it's fucking called. The Peeus.
-这想法挺棒啊  -你知道什么比这更棒吗
－ Fantastic idea. - You know another good idea?
我起来再去拿一盘吃的
Me getting up and getting another plate.
天啊 不要这样别拿了
Oh, God. No, don't. Don't.
利昂 差不多得了 伙计
Leon, come on, man.
-等我把这裤子解开  -老天
- And once I undo these pantsOh, jeez.
-解开这第一个扣子  -你会撑死的
...and this top buckle...- You're gonna get sick.
看好咯
Watch my smoke.
你这人什么毛病
What's wrong with you?
我要去咯拉里
I'm going in, Larry!
-老天啊  -噢太好了
Oh, Jesus. - LEON: Whoo! Oh, yeah.
瞧瞧这些雪蟹腿
Those snow crab legs.
-嘿 这些新鲜不  -新鲜 先生
Hey, these fresh? - SERVER: Yes, sir.
拿够了吧 你就坐下吃你的吧
It's enough already. Sit down and eat it.
不不不 你这样绝对不行
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
够了 这是你今天的最后一盘了
We're done. That was your last plate for today.
你已经吃了四盘了 太多了
You have four plates. Too much food.
我不许你再拿了够了
T'm cutting you off. That s all!
等等 你外面牌子上写着 尽情享用
Wait. You got a sign outside that says, "all you can eat. "
你现在跟我来说 我想怎么吃还不行了
You mean to tell me, I can't eat all the fuck want to eat?
只要你是个正常人 你想怎么吃都行
All you can eat if you are reasonable.
你已经吃了 我的朋友 我数着呢
You've already ate, my friend. I've been counting.
五磅的牛肋骨 十磅的明虾啊
Five pound short rib, ten pound prawns.
-顺便问下 你谁啊  -我是西蒙
- Who are you, by the way? - I'm Shimon.
-你就是西蒙  -我就是西蒙本蒙
You're Shimon? - I am Shimon.
噢 你就是这破地方的温蒂姐姐啊
Oh, so you're the Wendy's of this motherfucker.
我他妈就是温蒂 你还想让我戴上个红假发 点几个雀斑吗
I'm fucking Wendy. You want me to put on a little red wig and freckles?
-嗯嗯  -不如这样
Yeah. Yeah. How Jbout this?
-你不如试试  -你他妈给我滚出去后
How'bout you do that? - I do that
我就这么干
after you get the fuck out!
你永远不能再进这餐厅了 终生禁止
You're banned forever. Lifetime ban.
-终生  -那 那太不公平了
Lifetime. That's not that's not fair.
噢 你 我的朋友
Oh. You, my friend.
你想要来还能来这儿
You still can come when you want
因为你吃的和个正常人一样
because you eat like reasonable person.
嗯 是啊 我只吃了一盘 你猜为啥
Yeah. Yeah, I had one plate. You know why?
-因为这里的食物臭死了  -你才臭
Cause the food stinks. You stinkl
-不 你臭  -不 你才臭
No, you stinkl No, you stinkl
-你臭  -你才臭
You stink! LEON: You stinkl
-你臭  -你他妈臭死了
·You stinkl You fucking stink
-你才臭 西蒙  -不 你们都臭死了
- You stink, Shimon! - SHIMON: No, you stink.
滚出去 你们两个
Get out. Both of you out.
都给我滚出去 你 终生不许来
Both of you out. You, forever.
你 也许还有机会来
You, maybe- maybe you have a chance.
-去你妈的 温蒂  -终生禁止
Fuck you, Wendy. - Lifetime ban!
和你能相提并论的只有加里·布西了
Only person besides you, Gary Busey.
这里要是是家妓院 那我得气疯了
If this was a brothel, I'd be fucking pissed.
终生禁止 赶紧给我消失
Lifetime ban. You're gone.
-我没事吧  -你没事
- I'm still good? - SHIMON: You're still fine.
你没事 走吧
You're still fine. Go.
他对我太不公平了 太他妈不公平了
He did me dirty. He did me fucking dirty.
-是啊 他真的  -伙计 我现在要来点甜点
Yeah, he really did. - Wow, man. Now I need dessert.
什么 你疯啦 你已经吃了四盘了啊
What, are you nuts? You had four plates of food.
-你要来点不  -不了
You want something? - No.
不 好吧 别走开
No? Okay. Don't fucking leave me.
搞快点
Hurry up.
瞧瞧这谁啊
Look at this.
你知道吗 这 这时机正好
You know something? This is This is perfect.
我正好有个忙要请你帮
I have a favor to ask you.
-我在  -伙计 你这样开场
- I'm doing- - - Oh, boy, that's a horrible way
-有点糟糕啊  -不 听我说
to introduce a sentence. - TED DANSON: No, no.
我要演一部戏剧 它叫《自相纷争》
I'm doing a play. It's called House Divided.
-是吗  -是呢 我扮演林肯
- Yeah? - Yeah. I get to play Lincoln.
-什 你来扮演林肯  -是啊
- Wh- - You're playing Lincoln? - Yeah.
真有意思啊
What fun.
洛莉·路格林要演剧中我的妻子 玛丽·陶德
And Lori Loughlin is playing my wife, Mary Todd.
-洛莉·路格林吗  -是啊 洛莉·路格林
Lori Loughlin? - Yeah, Lori Loughlin.
-噢  -听着 听着
Oh. - And here's- here's the thing.
她喜欢打高尔夫 我就想着
She loves to play golf, and I was just hoping
你也许能在俱乐部帮她担保一下
that maybe you could sponsor her at the club.
-没别人愿意为她担保吗  -没有
There's nobody else who could sponsor her? - No.
就因为那个大学入学丑闻
Because of that whole college admissions scandal thing,
没有俱乐部想和她沾上关系了
no club will touch her.
-那太不公平了吧  -对啊 她人多好
That's not fair. - No. She's a lovely lady.
-是啊 我想也是  -这就是为什么我来
Yeah, I'll bet she is. - And that's why I'm coming- -
-她被俱乐部都拉入黑名单了  -是的没错
She's being blackballed from the clubs? - Yes. Yes.
那也太糟了 那简直 我会给她做担保
Terrible. That's- I'll sponsor her.
噢 拉里 谢了 老伙计
Oh, Larry. Thanks, man.
-很感谢你  -嗯 很开心能帮到你
- I really appreciate that. - Yeah. Happy to do it.
你也知道我喜欢保护弱者
You know I'm a champion of the underdog.
-你清楚的吧  -知道 知道
You know that. - I do. I do.
等一下 你和她一起工作过 不是吗
Wait a minute. You worked with her, didn't you?
对啊《宋飞正传》你们都参与过
Yeah. Yeah, on- on Seinfeld.
不不 那是前两年的事了
jlo, no, that was the last two years.
我没参与那集
I wasn't there for that episode.
但你写了最终集 对吧
But you did the finale, right?
-是啊 泰德 我是写了最终集  -和我想说的一样嘛
Yeah, Ted, I did the finale. - That's what I thought.
嗯 不管怎么说谢谢啊 我 我会告诉洛瑞的
Yeah. Anyway, thanks. I'II- - I'll let Lori know.
太感谢你了 伙计 我得走了
Thank you so much, buddy. I got to run.
登登 快看
Voila!
嗯
Yeah.
-瞧瞧你的样子啊  -随心所欲
LARRY: Lookat youSUSIE: "Catch as Caftan"
我的生意 我一手操办的
My business! All mine.
呃 你这样到处张贴自己的海报也挺好
Well, I like how you plastered yourself all over
-搞得好像这里是圣莫尼卡大道一样  -哎呀 营销嘛
Santa Monica Boulevard here- Ah, it's a sales thing.
搞得像 像你是奈费尔提蒂王后一样
Like- like Queen Nefertiti.
得花钱才能有回报嘛
You got to spend money to make money,
这是笔投资
and it's an investment.
我觉得我这生意必火
And I think the business is just gonna take off.
你也明白我为什么叫你来了
Now you see why I wantedryou to come.
好吧 呃 我得 我得走了
AlI right, well, I got to, uh, I got to take off.
-我今晚还有个重要的约会  -等下 厄玛不是已经和你分了吗
- I got a big date tonight. - Wait, Irma's gone, right?
是啊 这是分手后我第一次出来约会
Yeah. This is my first one.
-是我认识的人吗  -是的
- Anyone I know? - Oh, yeah.
-谁啊  -我不能告诉你
- Who? - I can't even tell you.
-得了吧 和我还有什么不能说的  -不能告诉你
Oh, come on! It's mel- I can't, no.
你会嘲死我的
You're gonna mock me to death.
我不会嘲笑你的 说吧
I'm not gonna mock. Tell me.
西恩娜·米勒
Sienna Miller.
她居然愿意和你约会一是啊
She's going out with you? - LARRY: Yeah!
-那个美得不行的女人  -是啊 我今晚要去
· That gorgeous woman? - Yeah, I'm going to her, uh,
参加她新电影的首映呢
screening for her new movie tonight.
-你来真的  -是啊
Oh, get the fuck out of here. - Yes.
-她对我有好感呢  -好吧
She's got a thing for me. - All right.
-呃 你知道这像什么不  -你知道为啥不
Well- - You know what it is? - You know why?
-嗯 我知道 我知道像什么  -对 亚特兰大
Yeah, I know. I know what it is. - Yeah. Atlanta.
听着 你和西恩娜约会的时候
Listen, when you're out with Sienna,
能不能提一嘴我的卡夫坦 毕竟它们那么好看
maybe mention the caftans, 'cause they'd look fantastic.
她那么高挑
She's tall, thin.
-这在她身上会很好看的  -你是
- It would flow beautifully on her. - Are you- -
你觉得她会穿这破玩意儿
Think she's gonna wear that fucking thing?
-没错  -想想都不可能
Yes! - Get out of here.
随心所欲
"Catch as Caftan. "
噢 我爱死了
Oh, I love it.
八十
"Fourscore..."
七年前
”...and seven years ago,
我们的先辈们在这块陆地上建立了一个新的国家
our fathers brought forth on this continent a new nation,
它孕育于自由
conceived in liberty..."
并奉行
...and dedicated to the proposition
人人生而平等的主张
that all men are created equal. "
八十七年前
"Fourscore and seven years ago..."
哦对了
LARRY: By the way,
你要是觉得你能分吃我的爆米花
if you think you're getting any of my popcorn,
那你就大错特错了
you're gravely mistaken.
大错特错
Gravely.
你要是觉得你和别人出来约会
If you think you can go on a date with someone
还不主动分享爆米花 那你才大错特错了
and not share popcorn, you're gravely mistaken.
-噢 所以这 这算个约会  -大错特错
Oh, is this- - Is this a date? - Gravely.
算是个约会吗
Is this a date?
不知道啊 拉里 你觉得呢
I don't know, Larry. You tell me.
如果你愿意分享爆半花 那这就算
If you share the popcorn, it's a date.
好吧
AlI right, well
-谢谢  -如果你非得吃的话
Thank you. - If you must.
我有点紧张
I get a little bit nervous.
紧张 来看的都是些朋友家人
Nervous? It's friends and family,
你有什么好担心的
you got nothing to worry about.
这会是你经历过最轻松的事了
This is the easiest thing you'll ever go through.
还有你 你不是还在拍另一部电影吗
And aren't you, uh, aren't you shooting another one?
-嗯 是在拍  -好忙的女孩儿啊
Mm. Right now. - Very busy gal.
-很忙的女孩儿  -嗯
· Busy gal. - Yeah.
我就像瑞秋和地毯商贩
I'm like Rachel and the rug merchants.
谁
Who?
瑞秋和地毯商贩
Rachel and the rug merchants.
-是啥  -是个
What's that? - It's like a- -
这是个很有名的旧约犹太寓言啊
It's a famous Old Testament Jewish parable.
-瑞秋和地毯商贩  -你从没听说过吗
- Rachel and the rug merchants? - Have you never heard of it?
-没听说过  -那你还管自己是犹太人
- Never heard of it. - Call yourself a Jew?
讲什么的
What's it about?
就是讲瑞秋和地毯商贩的
It's about Rachel and rug merchants.
什么 故事情节是什么 她是买到假的地毯了吗
What- - And what happened? Did she get cheated on a rug,
然后她不得不退还地毯吗
and she had to return the rug?
他们是卖错地毯了吗 地毯上是有污渍吗
Did they give her the wrong rug? Was there a stain on it?
我是说 这个故事
I mean, there's many possibilities
-能有很多可能性  -不 地毯上没有污渍
- for what the story...- No, no stain on the rug.
难道这块地毯对她的帐篷来说太大了
Was the rug too big for her tent,
然后她摆错方向了吗
and she got the dimensions wrong?
难道是讲她和地毯商贩之间的关系的
Was it about her relationship with the rug merchant?
她和地毯商贩是有一腿吗
Did she have an affair with the rug merchant?
她和地毯商贩之间发生啥了
What happened with her and the rug merchant?
强尼 强尼 你在哪里
Johnny? Johnny, where are you?
强尼
Johnny?
天啊 强尼 强尼 快出来吧
Oh my God. Johnny! Johnny, come on!
我发现你在电影里吃了好多水果
I notice you like to eat a lot of fruit in your movies.
我是说 虽然现在只放了一半
I mean, we're only halfway through this,
但你已经吃了一个甜瓜 一个油桃
and you've already eaten a cantaloupe, a nectarine,
还有一些桑葚
and some mulberries.
事实上 我仔细一想
In fact, now that I think about it,
你演《丑闻真相》的时候也吃了好多水果吧
didn't you eat a lot of fruit in Anatomy of a Scandal?
这是什么
What is that?
是你的表演方式吗
Is that part of your process?
你吃一囗 继续演 再吃一囗 再继续演
You take a bite, you act, you take another bite, you act.
我想认真看电影
I'm just trying to watch, you know.
-不好意思 不好意思  -抱歉哈
· SIENNA: Excuse me? Excuse me? - LARRY: Oh, sorry.
你有看到一个11岁的小男孩吗
Have you seen an 11- year- old boy?
你又开吃了
Oh, yeah. You're doing it again.
他穿着一件黑绿格子衬衫
He's wearing like a black and green checkered shirt.
他都失踪三小时了
He's been missing for, like, three hours.
不好意思 没看见
I haven't seen him. Sorry.
我的苍天啊
Oh, my God.
强尼
Johnny!
嘿 先生 你怎么回事
- Hey, chief. - What's up?
-强尼  -你叫我呢吗
· SIENNA: Johnny! - You talking to me?
是 想跟您说一下
Yeah. We got to have a little powwow.
有什么问题吗
Look, what's your problem?
我有问题 我没问题
My problem? I don't have a problem.
问题是您的外套有点
Your problem is that you're way in my area
-越界了  -没有 没有
- with your jacket. - No. No.
外套就应该放在椅子靠背上
That's where a jacket belongs, on the back of the chair.
这是我的椅子
It's my chair.
-谁规定的  -所以要放在这个靠背上
- In what world- - - So I get to put it on my back.
-别吵了  -我把它整齐优美地挂在
· SIENNA: Just leave it alone. - This is draped beautifully
我的靠背上
over the back of my chair.
没碍着任何人
·It's not disturbing anybody. -
-它垂到我腿上  -怎么
- It's draped...- Yes.
像给我跳大腿舞 我忍不了
...like you're giving me a lap dance, okay?
天哪 外套就应该挂在靠背上
Oh, please. Everybody knows that a jacket
天经地义
goes on the back of the chair.
你开车时
You drive a car,
难道要占尽所有车道吗
you go drive into every lane on the parkway, huh?
-不是这个理  -我结婚了
Yeah, no- - I'm married.
就不能在街上看上哪个女孩就和她睡
I can't just go to the mall and fuck any woman I want.
你们俩 都给我闭嘴
Excuse me. Both of you, stop it!
为什么你不挂在面前的椅子上
ATTENDEE: Why don't you put it on the front of his chair?
前面的椅子 你疯了
Put it on the front? What an idiot you are.
那他的脖子就要碰到我的外套
His neck is gonna be on my jacket.
我的外套就要挨着他的脖子
My jacket's gonna be on his neck.
你真的很莫名其妙
That doesn't make any sense at all.
-天哪 闭上你的臭  -你们俩都闭嘴 坐回去
- Oh, shut your fucking......- Both of you, shut up! Sit back!
放腿上吧
Just put it on the lap.
消停会儿
That's enough!
我们会帮你留心的
Well, we'll keep an eye out.
大事不妙 我有预感
Something's happened. I can feel it.
我有预感
I can feel it.
强尼
Johnny!
还是想告诉您 演得精彩
By the way, you're very good in this.
而我们
It is for us, rather,
要继续投身这前人
to be dedicated here to the great task
未竟的事业
remaining before us,
前人已然呕心沥血 我们更是要倾注全部
that from these honored dead we take increased devotion
为这伟大事业
to that cause..."-
前人愿意英勇斗争
- "...for which they gave
到最后一刻
their last full measure of devotion.
斗争到生命最后一刻
For which they gave their last full measure of devotion. "
会议下一项
AlI right, next on the agenda, we are reviewing
重申洛莉·路格林的入会申请
the membership application of Lori Loughlin.
在场有人
Is there anyone present
愿替她发言吗
who wishes to speak on her behalf?
我
I will.
大卫先生
Oh, Mr. David.
很开心见到您 请您开始
Nice to see you here. Floor is yours.
海景俱乐部的会员们 董事会成员们好
Members of Ocean View, our esteemed board.
87年前
Eighty- seven years ago,
我们的前人在这片土地上
our fathers brought forth on this property
开辟先例 成立这座高尔夫俱乐部
a new golf club dedicated to the proposition
以娱男性 女性排外
that men can have fun and women can't.
但历史在发展 时移世易
But that was a Iong time ago, and things have changed.
我们追求平等
For the better.
也许未来世界会忘记今天我们
The world will little note nor long remember
在蒙特卡洛会议室说了什么
what we say here in the Monte Carlo room,
但永远会记得我们的贡献
but it will never forget what they did here.
希兰·戈德法布
Men like Hiram Goldfarb,
组织了感恩节最佳球比赛
who started the Turkey Day best ball scramble,
威廉·雅各布森
and William Jacobson,
捐赠了这片地
who donated...that parcel of land.
我们今天才能在此打球
...where we play pickle ball.
我在此强烈建议
And I highly resolve
我们不该让这位女士
that she shall not have served
浪费光阴
her time in vain,
我们俱乐部一直推行
and that this exclusive club of specific people,
共有 共治 共享原则
by specific people, and for specific people
应该允许这位新女性加入
shall have a new, specific member.
就像亚特兰大那位
And as much as that woman in Atlanta ello#
想喝水的女性 洛莉·路格林也渴望
was thirsty for water, Lori Loughlin is equally thirsty
加入我们
- for membership!
我们应该欢迎她加入
I say we let her drink!
同意
Yes!
你成功了
You did it! -
什么你成功了 是我成功了
You did it? I did it.
我高兴傻了 是我成功说服他们了
What do I mean, "You did it"? I did it.
-你成功了  -啊
·You did! LARRY: Ah!
-我本有可能做个律师的  -哦 拉里
Could have been a great lawyer. - Oh. Larry.
或者一个屠夫 我会做得很开心的
Could've been a great butcher. And I would have enjoyed it too.
你操起木棍 锤击牛肉
You- - you take a mallet, you pound the beef.
使劲捶 使劲捶
·You pound it, you pound it. - Mm.
再片成薄片 真不错
You slice it. That's fun.
嗯 那加入俱乐部的事 我接下来 该做什么
Um, so, uh, as far as the club, what- - what next? What- -
你要和委员会的成员
You have to play two rounds of golf with, uh,
打两轮高尔夫 然后我来找你打
some of the committee members. And I'll be playing with you.
-很简单的  -太好了
- It'll be a breeze. Yeah. Oh, great!
拉里 一万个谢谢
Larry, I can't thank you enough.
人们嘴上说一万个 但都是骗人
You know, people say that, and- - and they don't really.
他们很快就不再感激了
They stop thanking.
估计你这回说完下次就不觉得感激了
You'll- - Probably won't thank me again after this.
实际上 如果你再说一句谢谢
In fact, if ever get another thank you from you,
我都要震惊了
uh, I'll be shocked.
我的天
Oh, my Godl
-我嘴里插了个老二吗  -直戳嘴边
- There's a dick in my mouth? - In your mouth.
-带蛋的  -一幅涂鸦 涂鸦
With balls? - A drawing. A drawing.
-有蛋 是涂鸦  -涂鸦而已
With balls. A drawing. - A drawing.
-涂鸦老二  -还不是戳进你的嘴
·Like a graffiti dick. - It's not in your mouth.
是轻擦你的唇
It's kind of grazing your lips.
他们让你的嘴轻擦那玩意儿
They grazed your lips with a dick.
-笑死我了  -他们毁了我的海报
How hilarious is that? - They ruined my poster,
-我的广告牌被毁了  -是的 为你难过
my billboard! They ruined it. - They did. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我还要再补充一个细节
I- - I have one- - one more detail to share.
-什么  -哈哈
What? - Uh- huh.
蛋在你怀里抱着
You're cradling the balls.
无意冒犯
I'm sorry. -
-轻擦且怀抱着  -笑死了
Grazing and cradling. - I'm sorry.
-是的  -真笑没了
Yeah. Oh, fuck me.
你在笑什么 杰夫 有什么好笑的
What are you laughing at, Jeff? What's so funny, Jeff?
-没 不好笑  -没什么好笑的
Yeah, that's not funny. It's- - It's not funny.
-一点儿也不好笑  -不好笑 我就是很震惊
No, it's not funny. No. - It is not. I'm...I'm shocked.
-不好笑  -没听过这种事所以笑了
No, it's not funny. It's shock laughing.
哪个狗杂种给老娘画的
Who the fuck would do that to me?
我不知道
I don't know.
我从不把那玩意儿放我嘴里 是吧 杰夫
I don't even put a dick in my mouth. Right, Je Jeff?
我不会吹箫
I don't give blowjobs.
为啥 你需要 想我做证明
What, do you need- - you need me to agree with you? I know.
你为什么不能时不时吹个箫呢
Why can't- - why can't you give a blowjob every now and then?
-拉里 你闭嘴  -你会难受死吗
Oh, Larry, come on. - Would that kill ya?
会吗
Would that kill ya?
-我真的可能会难受死  -啊 啊
You know, it might kill me. - LARRY: Huh? Huh?
怎么对这事这么反感
What is this revulsion?
而且关你什么事
And what difference does it make?
你是一单身汉
You're a single guy.
每天一个人在外面晃 招蜂引蝶
You're out there, single, hot on the town.
-是  -对对
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah, yeah.
可能一直有人愿意给你吹箫
You probably get em all the time.
-嘿  -一直有人
Hey. - Oh, all the time. Yeah.
你和西恩娜·米勒怎么样了
How did it, uh, how did it go with Sienna Miller? That's- -
-她不给你吹吧  -不顺
You didn't get one from her. - Not good.
-不顺  -真的 怎么回事
Not good Really? What happened?
我给她发了两次消息 一次也没回
I texted her twice. She never got back to me.
说得通 谁愿意要一个
Well, it wasn't gonna work out anyway
你这样的老男人呢
with an old fuck like you.
她和你在一起能有什么好处
What does she want to be with you for?
我同意 但是是她先对我有意思的
That's what I thought, but she's the one who started it.
看来她也先对你没意思了
Yeah, well, it looks like she ended it.
我要去给广告公司打电话了
I'm gonna go call the billboard company
把那玩意儿从我嘴里弄走
and get that dick out of my mouth.
说到西恩娜
Speaking of Sienna,
我认识她电影的导演
you know, I- I know the director on her movie.
-据他说  -哦 她现在正拍的那部
He says- Oh, the one she's filming now.
是他 他说她演技问题太多
Yeah. He says they're having a ton of problems.
-什么  -是 他们想和她
- What? - Yeah, they're thinking of,
解约
uh, firing her.
不可能吧
You're kidding.
说她演技不行
It's her acting.
我确实说过
You know, I did make a comment to her
她一直在电影里吃水果
about how she eats a lot of fruit in her movies.
如果说那是她演技的问题
I wouldn't be surprised if that's affecting
我倒能明白
her performance in this movie.
是种可能
It's a possibility.
我要去厕所了
I'm going to the bathroom.
嗯
All right.
八十七年前
"Fourscore and seven years ago,
我们的先辈在这个大陆上
our fathers brought forth on this continent
创建了一个新的国家 它孕育于自由
a new nation, conceived in liberty
并奉行人人生而平等的主张
and dedicated to the proposition that all men are created equal. "
够够的了
Enough already!
现在我们正从事一场伟大的内战
"Now we are engaged in a great civil war. "
嘿 西蒙 西蒙
Hey, Shimon! Shimon!
能和你说几句话吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
什么呀
What- - What is it?
你能先别跑了
Cou...Could you stop the jogging for a second,
-我们好谈谈吗  -我不能停
- so Ican talk to you? - Oh, I can't stop.
-为什么  -我什么要停下
Huh? - Why would Istop?
我正在慢跑
I'm in the middle of a jog
我知道 但是你这样蹦蹦跳跳
I know, but it's hard to have a conversation
我没法和你说话
with somebody who's bouncing up and down.
你想说什么就说
What is it? What do you need?
我觉得禁止我朋友
Well, I think it's a little harsh
一辈子不许进你的餐厅
to ban my friend for life from the restaurant,
-有点太苛刻了  -我这样打个比方
when really- Let me ask you a question.
-行  -你在床上
- Sure. In your bedroom
贴了个标语
you have a sign, let's say
当然只是假设 上面写着 尽情自慰
Let's say maybe you have a sign, "Masturbate all you want. "
-嗯  -自慰了一会 你说
Okay. - After a while, you say,
行了 不想做了
"No more. I can't. I don't want to do it anymore. "
对 因为井榨干了
Yeah, because the well runs dry.
里面没东西了啊
You know, there's no more water left.
-你不能  -不 可能还有东西呢
You can't. Oh, there can be water.
还有 但是一直做很羞耻
There can be water, but it's a shame- -
-你会觉得 够了  -不 不会羞
You say, "That's too much! "- No, no no, there'sno- -
如果你觉得羞耻 前五次你自慰时
If there was shame, you wouldn't have done it
-怎么没事  -利昂
five times to begin with. - Leon- -
为什么第六次会觉得羞耻
Why is there gonna be shame on number six?
不羞耻就不吧 利昂 我禁定了
Shame, no shame. Leon, he is banned.
-明白了吗  -我告诉你 我不想
Okay? - You know what? I- - I can't.
这样争论太粗鲁了
I can't. This is so rude.
-太粗鲁了  -很粗鲁
This is rude? I think- - - This is so rude
-我觉得这很粗鲁  -十分粗鲁
I think it is rude- - So rude
我觉得你挡着不让我跑步才粗鲁
I think you are rude for stopping me on my jog.
我还觉得你才粗鲁 写了个牌子
No, you're rude for putting up a sign
说 想吃多少吃多少 结果不让人吃
that says"all you can eat" when you don't mean a word of it.
你不用为此担心
You don't have to worry about this
因为你也终生被禁了
because you are banned for lifel
-啊 我也被禁了  -从现在起
Oh, I'm banned? - You are banned now!
-再见  -随意 我也不稀罕
Bye- bye! Yeah, like I give a shit
再进你家那破烂饭馆
if I ever enter that dump of a restaurant again.
我才不管你稀不稀罕
I don't care what shits you have
反正从此眼不见为净
because the shit is gone from my life.
-再见 煞笔  -走吧
Shalom, bitch- LARRY Okay.
哎 哎 哎 等一下 你来自以色列是吧
Uh, hey. Hey, hey You re from Israel
你听过瑞秋和地毯商人的故事吗
Are you familiar with Rachel and the rug merchants?
-是个圣经故事  -我知道圣经
- It's a Bible thing. I know the Bible.
但我从没听说过瑞秋
I've never heard of Rachel
也没听说过地毯商人
I've never heard of rug merchants.
-真的吗  -是
Really? SHIMON: Yeah.
-不是 你  -哦哦哦 瑞秋 对 对
No, you Oh, oh. Uh, Rachel, yeah, yeah
瑞秋 她看了一眼地毯商人
Rachel. She looks at the rug merchants
然后说 你被禁了 煞笔 再见
and says, "You're banned, bitch! "Shalom!
-嘿 嘿  -嘿 拉里
Hey, hey. Oh, hey, Larry.
再次感谢你的帮助
Thank you again forrall your help.
客气了 我的荣幸
Of course. Happy to do it.
我们今天最好还是别开球车了
You know, we probably shouldn't take a cart today
因为这只能走车道
'cause it's cart paths only.
我们没法走球道 因为会把球道压坏
We can't go on the fairway 'cause they punched the fairway.
没事 没事 我有这个
Oh, no, no problem, I- - I got this.
我有蓝旗 我们想开到哪去都行
Yeah, got the blue flag. We can drive anywhere.
我们甚至可以直接开到果岭
We can even drive right up to the green.
等会 你要拿到蓝旗得有
Wait a second. You got to have a doctor's note
-医生证明啊  -是
- to get one of those. - Oh, yeah.
我 我有艾巴氏病毒
Well, I- - I have Epstein- Barr.
你有艾巴氏病毒
You have Epstein- Barr?
一个血液专家是这么说的
One hematologist thinks so.
那其它血液专家怎么说的
What do the other hematologists think?
哦拉里 今天肯定玩的很开心
Oh, Larry, this is gonna be so much fun.
那不是种犹太病毒吗
Isn't that a Jew disease?
-这球漂亮啊  -谢谢
What a putt. Thank youl
真不错
LORI LOUGHLIN: Really good.
-真不错  -拉里
Really good. ·Larry.
这球你必须推进
You got to make this putt.
我们得赢点钱 打败他们俩
Come on, let's win some money. Let's beat these bastardls.
上 你可以的 上吧
Let's go. You got this. Let's go.
真行 拉里 你好好琢磨下果岭技巧吧
Great, Larry Way to read a green.
真行
Great.
谢谢 玩的真挺开心的
Oh, thank you, you guys. This was so much fun, really.
-是 不错  -谢谢
Oh, sure. That was great- Thank you.
-真不错  -谢谢
Yeah, it was great. - LARRY: Thank you.
《自相纷争》这周末首映
You know, A House Divided, it- it opens this weekend.
你们要不要来看 我给你们弄票
You guys want to come? I can get you tickets.
你和泰德那部对吧 我想看
Oh, you and Ted? Yeah, Ill see it.
-我也可以去  -是 非常感谢
- I'll come, Yeah. Thank you very much.
-那行  -谢谢
AlI right. Great. JEFF: Yeah, thank you.
哦 你得给他代客泊车票
Oh, you gotta give the guy your valet ticket.
不用 我不用 我有这个
Oh, no. I'm- I'm good. I've got this.
-残疾人贴纸  -老管用了这东西
·A handicapped sticker? - It's fantastic.
-我想停哪就停哪  -你怎么弄到的
- I can park anywhere. - How'd you get that?
-就是那个嘛  -哦对 艾巴氏病毒
Oh, you know. - Oh, yeah, Epstein- Barr
-就是那个嘛  -哦对艾巴氏病毒
Oh, you know. - Oh, yeah, Epstein- Barr.
-什么  -艾巴氏病毒
- What? - Epstein- Barr?
哦对 艾巴氏
Right. Epstein- Barr.
好了 享受好时光吧 拜
AJI right, you guys, enjoy the rest of your caiy. Bye.
-拜  -一拜
LARRY AND JEFF: Bye. - LORI: Bye.
对了 拉里 好好练练短击 好好练练
And, Larry, short game! Work on that short game.
是 是
Yeah, yeah.
我 天
Oh, my God.
八十七年前 我们的先辈
Fourscore and seven  years ago, our fathers. brought forth
在这块陆地上建立了一个新的国家 它孕育于自由
on this continent a new nation, conceived in liberty
并奉行人人生而平等的主张
and dedicated to the proposition that all men are created equal.
现在我们正在进行一场伟大的内战
Now we are engaged in a great civil war,
考验这个国家或任何一个
testing whether that nation
有着如此构想和理念的国家
or any nation so conceived and so dedicated,
是否能够长期存在
can long endure.
我们在这场战争中的
We are met on a great battlefield
一个伟大战场上集会
of that war.
我们在这里把战场的一角献给那些
have We are here to dedicate a portion of it
为了这个国家生存而
as a final resting place
献出生命的烈士
for those who here gave their lives
作为他们最后的安息之地
so that that nation might live. thc pc
但从更深远的意义来说 我们不能让这一角战场成为圣地
But in a larger sense, we cannot dedicate,
不能让它流芳百世 永垂青史
we cannot consecrate, we cannot hallow this ground. "
我们更应该不断的向这些烈士学习
"It is rather that from these honored dead,
学习他们鞠躬尽瘁的献身精神
we take increased devotion to that cause
我们更该下定决心
and that we here highly resolve that these dead
不让这些烈士的鲜血白流
shall not have died in vain
这个民有
and that government of the people,
民治
by the people,
民享的政府
for the people,
将会万古长存
shall not perish from the earth. "
好样的
ONLOOKER 1: Yeah, buddy! - ONLOOKER 2: Whoo!
美利坚合众国 美利坚合众国
CROWD: USA! USA!
去你妈的 西蒙
Yeah! Fuck you, Shimon!
这就是五磅的牛小排和十磅的去你妈的
That's five pounds of short ribs and ten pounds of fuck you!
草泥马 西蒙
Fuck you, Shimon!
嘿 说来你们都不敢信
Hey, you re not gonna believe this
Hey, you're not gonna believe this.
我刚跟我们的首席财务官通完话
I just got off the phone with my CFO.
生意好的不行
Business, booming.
-好到爆  -什么
Through the roof What?
对 就过去两周 难以置信
Yeah. In the past two weeks. Unbelievable.
-老二  -不是老二好嘛
It's the penis. - SUSIE: Oh, it's not the penis.
-就是老二  -是产品好
It's the penis! - It's the product!
那老二画上去之前
How come it wasn't booming
生意怎么没好到爆
before the penis got up there?
-口碑啊  -口碑
It's word of mouth. Oh, yeah, word of mouth.
嘿 我觉得这就是老二刺激了生意
Hey, I think you're getting a post- penis bump.
-怎么刺激的  -因为人们会说
How? - Becauseipeople are talk- -
嘿 你看到广告牌上那个
"Hey, did you see the woman with the billboard
卖卡夫坦的女人了吗 她嘴里含着个老二
with the caftans? There's a penis in her mouth. "
嘴里有个老二吗 嘴里含个老二
"Penis in her mouth? ”"There's a penis in her mouth. "
对
Yeah.
你搞得跟演音乐剧似的
You sound like you're in a musical.
对我来说 这可是真实的生活
Yeah, well, to me, it's real life.
-我需要把它弄掉  -不 实际上
And I want it down. - No. In fact...
-你知道你该怎么做吗  -什么
You know what you should do? - What?
再画一个老二
You need a second dick.
-再来一个  -不
Second dick. - No.
你觉得要是再来一个我的生意能更好
You think I'm gonna get more business from two dicks?
-肯定翻倍  -对
It'lldouble! JEFF: Uh, yeah.
你知道我怎么想的吗
You know what I'm thinking?
-后面再来一个  -够了
Dick up the ass SUSIE: Oh, stop it.
-你们俩可真恶心  -所以 两个老二画前面
- You're disgusting. JEFF: So, two dicks up front,
-后面再来一个  -对
dick up the ass. - Yeah.
-再弄点精液在上面  -对
And how bout some jizz on ya? - LARRY: Yeah
我跟你说哈
You know what? Let me tell you- -
这样一来你就会卖脱销 脱销
I mean, you will sell out. Sell out.
来点精液 肯定会取得巨大成功
Little jizz. Jizz will knock it out of the park.
沃伦·巴菲特可从没制定过一个
Warren Buffett never made a business plan
脸上有精液的商业计划 好吧
having jizz on the face. All right. Trust me on that.
我就是说 作为一个商业女性
Yeah, I'm just saying as a businesswoman,
你有责任考虑一下这事
it's incumbent on you to consider this thing.
-我会考虑的  -老二不能擦
- I'll think about it. Stick with the dicks!
-走开  -西恩娜 是拉里
SIENNA: Goaway! ·LARRY: Sienna, it's Larry.
-我 我需要跟你谈谈  -拉里 现在不行
I- I need to talk to you. - SIENNA: Larry, not now.
我现在情况不好 拉里
It's a really bad time, Larry.
就几分钟 很重要
It- - It'll only take a few minutes. It's important.
有话快说
What's up?
好吧 首先
Uh, well, first of all,
我 我想为那晚的事向你道歉
I- - I just wanted to apologize, uh, for the other night.
就是我把外套放到了椅子后面
You know, I put the coat on the back of the chair.
可外套就该放那啊
That's where coats go. -
衣服不一直都是放那的吗
LARRY: That's where coats have gone for forever.
即便是莎士比亚的时代
Even in Shakespeare's time,
他们也会把披风和紧身上衣放椅子背上
they put the capes and doublets on the back.
行吧
Yeah. You know.
我现在没空想这些外套的事 拉里
It's the least of my worries right now, Larry,
但还是谢谢你能来道歉
the coat, but thank you for the apology.
电影拍的还顺利吗
How's everything going with the filming?
不顺利
It's not good.
不管怎么做 我就是搞不定
No matter what I do, I just can't get a handle on it.
非常抱歉听你这么说
I'm really sorry to hear that.
简直是噩梦 他们可能会赶我走
It's a nightmare. They're gonna fire me.
我在拖车里看了看
You know, uh, I'm looking around this trailer,
发现这里没有水果
and I notice there's no fruit.
我都不 我不喜欢水果
I don't evenI don't like fruit.
我甚至都 我不 你什么意思啊
I don't even- - I don't- What do you mean?
你不喜欢吃水果
Oh. Uh- huh. Oh, you don't- - You don't like fruit.
-不 我不喜欢  -好吧
No, I don't like fruit. - LARRY: Oh, sure. Yeah.
我不在乎水果 所以
I don't care for fruit, particularly, so...
你不在乎 你不喜欢
You don't care for it? You don't like it?
-你不吃  -拉里 我不需要
You don't eat it? - Mm- mm. Larry, I don't need it.
我不在乎 我
I don't care for it, particularly. I- -
我给你带了个梨
I got you a pear.
我去给你煮点咖啡
I'll make some coffee.
会是谁呢
SIENNA: Who could that be?
你好夫人
SOLDIER: Hello, ma'am.
-请问是塔尼亚·巴斯托吗  -是我
- Are you Tanya Barstow? - Yes.
哈罗德
SIENNA: Harold.
他的飞机被击中了
His plane was shot down.
他死了
He's dead.
他说过我们会乘船去岛上
He said we'd sail to the islands,
就我们两个
just the two of us.
我很快就回来 他说
"I won't be long, "he said.
等我回来的
"When I get back, "he said.
整个世界都在我们眼前 他说的
"We have the whole world in front of us, "he said.
可时间没听到他的话
But time doesn't listen,
世界也没有等我们
and the world doesn't wait.
我求过他 我求过他不要参加空军
I begged him! I begged him not to go to the Air Force.
我求他不要去开飞机
I begged him not to fly.
都是你的错
It's your fault.
是你鼓励他去飞行学校
You encouraged him to go to flight school.
你就是想让他去送死
You wanted him to die!
该死的明明是你
You're the one who should be dead.
我恨你
- I hate you! ·
咔
DIRECTOR: Cut! -
太棒了
DIRECTOR: That's great.
-西恩娜 太漂亮了  -是 演的太好了
Sienna, oh, that was beautiful. - DIRECTOR: Yeah, that was amazing.
好棒啊
How great was that?
-太感人了  -谢谢
That was sensational. - Thank you.
-你真棒  -我天
You were amazing. Oh, my God.
西恩娜 你演的太好了
LARRY: Wow. - Sienna, that was great.
-我真是开心死了  -没问题是吧
I'm just thrilled. We got it, right?
-绝对啊  -没问题
Yes, absolutely. ·LARRY: Got it.
-你救了我  -继续
You saved my fucking ass. DIRECTOR: Moving on!
-来一个  -来一个哈
SIENNA: Come on. - Come on, huh?
-真行  -真行
Come on. Come on. Come on.
给力
Come on.
真不敢相信你居然做到了
I cannot believe that you did that.
你帮我想明白了
You figured it out for me.
我告诉你我没想明白什么
I'll tell you what I can't figure out.
我研究了很久瑞秋和地毯商人的故事
I tried doing some research on Rachel and the rug merchants,
但我 我什么都查不到 哪都没有
and Ican't- - I can't come up with anything. I can't find it.
-奇怪  -是啊
Weird. Yeah.
你们的宗教信仰里那么多故事
SIENNA: Of all the stories that I read in your religion,
就这个故事特别触动我
she was the one that really, like, spoke to me.
你确定你看过 有没有可能是你梦到的
You're sure you read it? Is it possible you dreamed it?
听着 我不
Okay, iook, I don't- -
我不知道我在哪读过 我不 我不记得在哪看到的了
I don't know where I read it. I don't- ∴I can't remember where I read it,
但我知道肯定有这故事
but I know it definitely exists.
-好吗  -好吧
Okay? Yeah. - LARRY: Okay.
还有一个词 就是你说的那个schmeitz
You know what else I tried to find was the word schmeitz,
我 我怎么也没查到
which. ...I couldn't find that either.
有这个词啊
Schmeitz exists.
-schmeitz  -就是
Schmeitz? Schmeitz is a real word
我该走了的意思
for"I've got to go. "³Igot to schmeitz. "
这个假发折磨死我了
- This wig is killing me.
特别不舒服
It's so uncomfortable.
我得找人给我调整一下
I think I have to go get it adjusted.
你每部电影都会戴不同的假发吗
Do you wear a different wig in every movie?
现在想想看
Now that I think about it,
我觉得你的头发
I don't think I've ever seen you
好像就没有重样过
with the same hair. In fact,
我甚至不知道自己看没看过你的真头发
I don't know if I've ever seen your real hair.
你是金发 褐发
Are you blonde? Are you brunette?
红发 还是什么
Are you redhead? What- -
我 我都不知道你发型本来啥样
I- I don't even know what your hair looks like.
我脱发 他妈的你个老混蛋
I have alopecia, you fucking asshole
-我又不知道你脱发  -混蛋
- I didn't know you had alopecia! - Asshole!
别走 别走啊
Don't schmeitz! Don't schmeitz!
我又不知道她脱发 你知道她脱发吗
I didn't know she had alopecia. Did you know?
-我不知道  -就是啊 谁知道啊
I had no idea. LARRY: Yeah, who knew?
-怎么可能看得出来嘛  -就是说
How can you tell? - You can't.
拉里 嘿 准备好了吗
Larry! Hey! You ready?
有没有感觉要当个赢家了
You feeling like a winner?
-是啊  -不错
Oh, yeah. - Oh, good.
-感觉像个大赢家  -不错 拉里 真不错
Feeling like a big winner. - LORI Good, Larry, good,
毕竟我可不喜欢输哦
cause I do not like to lose.
对了 你是怎么把开球时间改到10点45的
By the way, how did you get the tee time switched to 10: 45?
-我就约不到10点45场啊  -哦是吗
- I couldn't get the 10: 45. - Oh, crazy thing.
可能开球员喜欢我吧 真奇怪
Starter just likes me. Weird.
好了 我要去球场了
AlI right, I'm gonna go to the range.
-行  -一起去球场吗
- Okay. LORI: Wanna go to the range?
到 到时候球场见
I'll- - I'll meet you there.
好了 少叭叭 多动动
AIl right. Less chit chatting and more chipping.
-行  -走吧 好了
Okay. - Let's go. All right.
-行  -我们肯定要赢咯 拉里
Okay. - We're gonna win, Larry.
赢点小钱
Take some money today!
-玩得开心  -嘿 戴维德
Have fun Hey, Daveed.
嘿 你怎么样
Hey. How you doing?
-早上好啊  -早
Good morning- Morning.
呃 我就是好奇问下
Um, I'm just curious.
洛莉是怎么把开球时间改到10点45的
How did Lori get that tee time moved to 10: 45?
我能想到无数个理由
I can think of 50 reasons.
嗯 她挺有一套的哈
Yeah. She's quite a gal, huh?
是啊 她真有自己一套的
Yeah, she's quite a gal.
-可不是吗  -行吧 谢谢
Yes, she is. - All right. Thank you.
-行 打得不错  -真假的
Okay. That's good. - MATT: Oh, really?
-嗯 我得承认确实不错  -这可是五杆
Yeah. I'm gonna give you that. - That is five.
我也打出了五杆 我们现在领先一杆
I got a five also, so we're up by one.
-确实 你说的对  -确实
That's true. Right. Yes. - That's right.
-你要被比下去了哦 马特  -行
You're going down, Matt. Yeah. - Okay.
嘿 你球杆落那儿了  -谢谢你提醒我 拉里
Hey, you left your club over there. - Oh, thank you, Larry.
你打出了五杆
You got a five?
-是啊  -你怎么打出五杆的
Yeah. - How did you get a five?
-我找到了我的球  -你找到那个球了
- I found my ball. - You found that ball?
-我找到了  -你怎么从树林里搞出来的
- I found that ball. - How'd you get it out of the woods?
你那球打得挺远的啊
You were pretty deep in there.
我球位不错
I had a good lie.
好吧 你球位确实不错
Yeah, you had a good lie all right.
我去
Holy shitl
拉里人呢 他妈的人在哪儿呢
Where's Larry? Where the fuck is he?
-他说他会  -再迟到一次
He said he'll be- - - Late again?
-不 他说他会来的 信我 他会准时到的  -老天
- No, he'll be here. Trust me, he'll be here. Jesus.
-我都不  -嘿
- I don't even really- - - Hey!
嘿 你就是那个嘴里有老二的女的
Hey. You're that lady with the dick in her mouth.
真的要这么干吗
Really?
听着 我也不想这么干的
Look, I'm sorry for doing this.
我妻子要求我这么干 你就听我的好吗
My wife wants me to do this, so just go along with it.
我数到三 你就把头往右转
On the count of three, turn your head to the right.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
没错 没错 别他妈的用你这张臭嘴
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. And keep my wife's business
议论我老婆的事
out of your motherfucking mouth!
你有点东西啊 老伴儿
You are really something, boy.
-那一打太性感了 宝贝儿  -嘿
Oh, that was hot, baby! - Hey.
噢拉里 你不会相信刚刚发生什么了的
Oh, Larr, you're not gonna believe this.
噢不不 你不会相信我看到的这个的
Oh, no, no, you're not gonna believe this.
今天下午我开车经过那块广告牌
I drove by the billboard this afternoon.
你嘴里又有一根老二了
There's a second dick in your mouth!
你要大赚一笔了
You're gonna make a fortune!
哇哦 第二根
Wow. Second dick.
天啊
Oh, God.
你应该去看一眼的 可大了
LARRY: You should see this one. It's huge!
抱歉 抱歉
So, so sorry. So sorry.
你 你可以直接起身的啊 又不会把你怎么样
You- - you could've gotten up. It wouldn't've killed you.
位置不错啊 很高兴见到你
Well, they're good seats. It's nice to see you.
嗯
Yeah.
要看剧了好激动啊
I'm excited about this.
-你激动吗  -嗯 我也很激动
Are you excited to see this? - Yeah, I am.
我真的好爱洛莉·路格林
I really like Lori Loughlin.
是啊 她可不一般啊
Oh, yeah. Quite a gal.
嘿 我认识你
Hey. I know you.
你是那个中餐馆的服务员啊 对吧
You're a waiter at that Chinese restaurant, right?
是的 我在日华宫端盘子
Oh, yes. I work at Sun Wah Palace.
那死鱼怎么样了
How's the dead fish?
-他  -还死着吗
·He- - - Still dead?
噢 你就是上次那个关心鱼的家伙 不 我们没死鱼
Oh. You the fish guy? No. We no have dead fish.
我们 来市中心的餐馆看 鱼还在呢
We- - Visit downtown restaurant. You see fish there.
-鱼好好的呢 更快活了  -我 我这
- Very happy. Doing better there. - Ah, I'm...I'm gonna go- -
-我这周末去  -好啊
- I'm gonna go this weekend. - Okay.
嗯 那啥 你是历史迷吗
Yeah, what, are you a big history buff?
-喜欢林肯  -噢是的
You like Lincoln? - Oh, yes.
我最爱的总统之一
One of favorite president.
要是林肯也有个鱼缸
You know, if Lincoln had a fish tank
然后有鱼也卡在滤水器里了
and a fish got stuck in the filter,
林肯肯定会把鱼救出来的
Lincoln would've freed the fish.
呃 鱼没卡住 所以林肯没有鱼可以解放
Uh, fish not stuck, so Lincoln no have fish to free.
这只是个假设 林肯肯定也会解放鱼的
It's a hypothetical. Lincoln would free fish.
你为什么这么关心一条鱼
Uh, why you care so much about fish?
-你为什么不关心  -还是考虑考虑你自己吧
- Why you no care about fish? - Maybe you worry about yourself.
-嗯  -你这人有问题 先生
- Yeah. - You have problem, sir.
不 你这人才有问题 你个可悲的撒谎精
No, you have problems. You pathological liar.
-可悲的撒谎精  -嘿
- You pathological liar. - Hey.
-不 鱼病了  -嗯 鱼卡住了
No. Fish sick. - Yeah. Fish stuck.
-不 鱼能动  -鱼死了 鱼死了
No, fish move. - Fish dead. Fish dead.
你干嘛呢 我们是来看剧的
What are you doing? We're here to watch a play.
-好吧  -好了
Yeah. - Okay.
-玛丽   -是 亚布
- Mary. - Yes, Abe.
你有看到过我的红色长袜吗
Have you seen my red stockings?
你是说那个布满了洞洞的长袜
You mean the ones that were riddled with holes?
我都没注意到
I hadn't noticed.
我注意到了 我让米兰达把它们全扔了
I had, and I had Miranda throw them out.
或者用你可能会喜欢的方式来说
Or to put it a way you might appreciate,
它们已经得到解放了
they've been emancipated.
我们或许应该比计划中晚点到
Perhaps we should arrive a little later to the Sewards'
苏厄德家
than we planned.
守时是君王的礼节 我们不应该迟到
Punctuality is the politeness of kings. We shan't be late.
啊 他要是再提一次
Ah. If he talks about wanting to purchase Alaska
想购买阿拉斯加地区这件事 我就加入邦联
one more time, I will join the Confederacy.
弗朗西斯·苏厄德视我为尘土
Frances Seward thinks I'm dirt.
-她要是再这样  -嘿
- If she looked down her nose...- Hey.
目中无人 我发誓她眼珠都得给瞪出来
...any further at me, I swear her eyes would fall out.
-干啥  -你没把外套
- What? - You have not draped the coat
在椅背上搭好
over the back of the seat properly.
-我外套搭得挺好的  -外套太长了
- My coat fine. - Coat long.
外套搭好了
Coat fine.
外套太长了 还有鱼死了
Coat long. And fish dead.
八十七年前
Fourscore and seven years ago,
我们的先辈们在这块陆地上建立了一个新的国家
our fathers brought forth on this continent a new nation,
它孕育于自由 并奉行
conceived in liberty and dedicated to the proposition
人人生而平等的主张
that all men are created equal.
如今 我们正在进行一场伟大的内战
Now we are engaged in a great civil war,
考验着这个国家或任何一个
testing whether that nation, or any nation so conceived.
有如此构想和理念的国家
...and so dedicated,
是否能够长期存在
can long endure.
嘿 我要去上个厕所
Hey. I have to go to the bathroom.
-不行  -我要尿尿
No. - I have to pee.
不行
No- -
他正在
He's in the middle- -
我每次尿尿
I've been memorizing the Gettysburg Address
都会背诵葛底斯堡演说
every time I pee,
我现在一听到就忍不住想尿尿
and I'm conditioned to pee when I hear it.
那些为此牺牲的烈士们
For those who here gave their lives.
-这  -就像巴甫洛夫条件反射一样
·This- - - It's like a Pavlovian response.
行了 这就有点荒唐了
Okay, that's ridiculous.
-不 一点也不荒唐好吗  -他
No, it's not ridiculous- He- -
-他正在发表演说呢  -我知道啊
·He's in the middle of it. - I understand.
你就憋着吧
You're just gonna have to hold it.
-嗯  -好了
Yeah. - Okay.
但从更深远的意义来说 我们不能让这一角战场成为圣地
But in a larger sense, we cannot dedicate,
不能让它流芳百世 永垂青史
we cannot consecrate, we cannot hallow this ground.
那些英勇的人 不论死去还是活着的
The brave men, living and dead...
曾在此奋战过的 已经使它神圣化
...who struggled here have consecrated it...
我不行了
I can't- -
憋不住了 憋不住了
It's bad. It's bad.
赶紧把这外套拿开 我的脚
Get this coat out of the way! My foot!
-你在干什么  -脚卡住了
WAITER: What are you doing? - Foot stuck!
-脚没卡住  -脚卡住了
WAITER: Foot not stuck. - Foot stuck!
-脚没卡住  -脚 卡住了
WAITER: Foot not stuck. - Foot... stuck!
他没事吧
Is he okay?
老天啊
Oh, boy.
而这个
·Ew! - And that government
民有 民治 民享的政府
of the people, by the people, for the people shall not perish
将会万古长存
from the earth.
拉里 服了 伙计 你搞什
Larry, come on, man, what the- -
搞什么鬼
What the fuck!
我的老天
Oh, my God.
什
Wha- -
噢 西恩娜 我天
Oh, Sienna. Oh, my God.
老天
Oh, boy.
得了 我
Oh, come- - Me?
什么 老天
What? Oh, please.
-晚上好 先生  -嘿 晚上好
- Good evening, sir. - Hey, good evening.
你知道你刚刚在那儿违规掉头了吗
You realize you made an illegal U- turn back there?
老实说 警官 要是我早知道那是违法的
Honestly, officer, had I known it was illegal,
我也不会这么干对吧 我是说当然不知道
would I have done it? Of course, not.
你有什么理由可以解释下你没注意到吗
Is there any reason that you weren't paying attention?
你看到那块广告牌了吗
You see that billboard up there
有西恩娜·米勒的那块
with Sienna Miller?
你看到上面画的了吗
You see what's going on up there?
你应该清楚这片居民区的广告牌上
You do know we've had a rash of these penises on billboards
-出现了很多这种老二吧  -真糟 真糟
all over this neighborhood? - Terrible. Terrible.
重点是
The thing is,
我看到了那块广告牌 然后我说
I saw that billboard, and I went,
老天 我得给这拍张照
"Oh, my God, I got to get a picture of this.
那可是西恩娜·米勒啊 我和她约过会呢
It's Sienna Miller. "I had a date with her.
-我们约过 嗯  -就你
·We had a Yeah. - You?
先生 你 你看起来
Sir, you're- - you're like 50 years
-比她老了快50岁了  -是是
older than she is. - Yes, yes,
我是比她大了很多 但其实是她追的我
I am considerably older, but she pursued me, actually.
没跟你吹呢 我知道很难相信这话
To tell you the truth. I know it's hard to believe,
但真的是她追的我
but she did.
顺便说下 广告牌上画这些老二
By the way, that movie's gonna do gangbusters
-这电影绝对会爆火的  -先生 这说的有点恶心了
· with those penises up there. - Sir, that's sick.
不 我朋友的妻子有个卡夫坦生意
No, my friend's wife had a caftan business,
她也搞了块广告牌 然后有人在她嘴里
and she had a billboard, and somebody drew dicks
画了老二 结果她生意就大红大紫了
in her mouth and business took off.
大卫先生
Mr. David,
你能解释下为什么你车后座有
can you explain to me why you have a box of spray paint
一袋喷漆罐吗
in the back of your car?
我就老实跟你讲吧
I'm gonna be perfectly honest with you.
我和我朋友去了这个宣传说尽情享用的餐馆
My friend and I went to this all- you- can- eat restaurant.
他吃太多螃蟹了 然后他们就禁止我们再去了
He ate too many crabs, and they banned us.
所以我俩回去 然后给它标语喷漆写上
And so we went back and spray painted,
不能尽情享用
"Not all you can eat. "
你这又亲口认了另一个罪
You just admitted to another crime.
-请下车 先生 先生  -明明就不是尽情享用
· Step out of the car, sir. Sir. - But it's not all you can eat.
-简直是一派胡言  -马上
It's bullshit. Now.
-明明就是不能尽情享用好吗  -请立马下车
- It's not all you can eat. - Out of the car now.
-这不是我干的  -太恶心了
- Oh, I didn't do that. - That's disgusting.
你不会觉得是我画的那些老二吧
You think I drew those dicks up there?
-嗯  -我连老二都画不来
Yeah. - I can't even draw a dick.
我都不会画画
I don't know how to draw.
我会画 会画一对胸吧大概
I can draw- - I can draw a breast maybe.
-嗯  -我根本画不来老二啊
Yeah. - I can't draw a dick.
-这 这  -嗯
That- - that's- - - Yeah.
-我是不会画老二的  -还是挺恶心的
- I would never draw a dick. - Still disgusting.
我又不知道她有脱发症
I didn't know she had alopecia!